[
 {
   "Front": "ἀγάπη, ἡ",
   "Back": "Love"
 },
 {
   "Front": "γῆ, ἡ",
   "Back": "Earth, land, ground"
 },
 {
   "Front": "ζωή, ἡ",
   "Back": "Life"
 },
 {
   "Front": "φωνή, ἡ",
   "Back": "Voice, sound"
 },
 {
   "Front": "ἀλήθεια, ἡ",
   "Back": "Truth"
 },
 {
   "Front": "ἁμαρτία, ἡ",
   "Back": "Sin"
 },
 {
   "Front": "βασιλεία, ἡ",
   "Back": "Kingdom, reign"
 },
 {
   "Front": "δόξα, ἡ",
   "Back": "Glory, majesty"
 },
 {
   "Front": "ἐκκλησία, ἡ",
   "Back": "Congregation, assembly, church"
 },
 {
   "Front": "ἡμέρα, ἡ",
   "Back": "Day"
 },
 {
   "Front": "καρδία, ἡ",
   "Back": "Heart"
 },
 {
   "Front": "δέ",
   "Back": "And, but, now"
 },
 {
   "Front": "καί",
   "Back": "And, even, also"
 },
 {
   "Front": "μέν",
   "Back": "On the one hand, indeed"
 },
 {
   "Front": "ὁ, ἡ, τό",
   "Back": "the"
 }
]